redlioneducation.com 2011-12-31

# Redlioneducation.com

**Privacy Policy**

**Information Collected by RedlionEducation**

**Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information**

RedlionEducation collects various types of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies. The type of information your browser or Internet session may automatically provide us with can include the browser you are using, your Internet domain, the operating system on your computer, your IP address and the URL you saw just before coming to the RedlionEducation site, the pages of the site you visited and the URL of the page you visited upon leaving the site. 

RedlionEducation may also contract with reputable third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect your non-personally identifiable information.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

All personally identifiable information you provide is maintained in confidence by RedlionEducation. There are instances, however, in which your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. 

Your non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of RedlionEducation on an anonymous basis. 

When you request information from RedlionEducation or any university affiliated on the website, we may transfer that information within RedlionEducation or route your information to university, across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world, so that they may provide the information on the program that you requested. 

We may also disclose information to a third party who provides substantially similar services as the original service about which you requested more information. In such situations, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing. Please be aware that RedlionEducation is very careful in selecting companies with whom it does business. 

In addition to the above situations where your information may be shared with others, there is also the possibility that RedlionEducation, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. In the event of such transaction, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to all collected personally identifiable information. 

Finally, RedlionEducation may share your information as necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials.

**Security**

Wherever your personally identifiable information may be held within RedlionEducation or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information you shared with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Please note that while RedlionEducation will make every reasonable effort to protect your information, no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure. 

**Choice**

**Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Use of Cookies & Opting-Out**

Some of our web sites utilize cookies to collect information about your website activities and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting RedlionEducation web sites. 

**Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Opting-Out**

You may choose whether or not to provide personally identifiable information to RedlionEducation. If you choose to provide such information to RedlionEducation, you have the right to tell us not to make some of the uses of such information described herein or may have such information deleted in its entirety. 

**Access/Accuracy**

To the extent that you do provide us with personally identifiable information, RedlionEducation wishes to maintain the accuracy of this information. Where we collect personally identifiable information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting RedlionEducation should you need to update or correct that information. 

**Children's Privacy**

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), RedlionEducation is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

**Commitment**

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and RedlionEducation's web sites are constantly changing to meet these demands. 

While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as practicable after you bring it to our attention. 

**Your Consent**

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to RedlionEducation's processing of personally identifiable information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy. 

RedlionEducation.com may also share the information you submit to online and offline schools and to marketing partners in the education industry. This information may be used to contact you via phone, email or postal mail to ask about your interest in enrolling. 

**Contacting Us**

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding RedlionEducation's Privacy Policy, you may email us at

Privacy

**RedlionEducation.com**  
826 ORANGE AVE   
CORONADO, CA 92118  
Phone 619-405-3827   
Fax 619-566-4014

Thank you for visiting our web site. We hope you have a pleasant experience while you are here.
